Okay. Um, now that you've successfully
created this, you are going to want to
um add some collaborators possibly. If
you're working by yourself, you might
not want to, but if you're trying to add
collaborators to your GitHub um
repository, this is how you do it.
You'll click on settings, and then
you'll click on collaborators, and it is
going to need you to verify. So, I'm
going to send myself an email to verify.
You may have dual factor authentication
set up with an authenticator app. Um, in
that case, you'll enter the code. Um,
but I'm going to verify and I'm going to
pause this video while I do.
All right, we have successfully gotten
in. And so what I'm going to do is I'm
going to add some collaborators. So you
can add people. You could search for
them by their email or um you could
search. So we could do testgmail.com
and see if someone has that and we could
invite them or um you can search for
them by username. So, I could search for
um someone by username um and I could
invite them um so or you could search
them by their full name. Um in this
case, I'm going to invite my other
account
and I'm going to add them as a
collaborator. And now they have been
added as a collaborator. And in the next
video, we'll talk about how to accept a
collaboration request.